Guide to the Gordon Moore Papers M1965
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 4: Photographs and Slides, 1964-2001
  - Intel Analysts Meeting [Originally in Box 159, Folder 11], 1991 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Caltech Watson Lecture and UofC Berkeley [Originally in Box 159, Folder 13], 1991 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Corporate Overview [Originally in Box 159, Folder 14], undated (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Society of Security Analysts [Originally in Box 159, Folder 15], 1991 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - MIT Leaders for Manufacturing [Originally in Box 159, Folder 16], 1991 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Intel N-11 Announcement [Originally in Box 159, Folder 17], 1991 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Microcontamination Conference [Originally in Box 159, Folder 18], 1991 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Hot Chips VII Stanford University [Originally in Box 160, Folder 1], 1995 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - SPIE - International Society for Optical Engineering Microlithography Symposium [Originally in Box 160, Folder 2], 1995 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Robertson Stephens Semiconductor Conference [Originally in Box 160, Folder 3], 1995 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Dataquest Semiconductor Industry conference [Originally in Box 160, Folder 4], 1993 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - VLSI Multilevel Interconnection Conference [Originally in Box 160, Folder 5], 1993 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - American Physical Society Meeting [Originally in Box 160, Folder 6], 1993 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - SIA Semiconductor Technology Workshop [Originally in Box 160, Folder 7], 1992 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Silicon Valley Personal Computer Design Conference [Originally in Box 160, Folder 8], 1992 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Columbia Institute Inland Empire Economic Summit [Originally in Box 160, Folder 9], 1992 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - FAE Conference [Originally in Box 160, Folder 10], 1992 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - SIA/SRC Washington Conference [Originally in Box 160, Folder 11], 1992 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Monte Jade Science and Technology Center Association Conference [Originally in Box 160, Folder 12], 1992 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Graphs, Charts and photos of Intel Products [Originally in Box 161, Folder 1], 1970-1979 (Box 82)
  - Photographs of people, graphs articles and notes [Originally in Box 162, Folder 1], 1971-1972 (Box 83)
  - IEEE Electron Devices Meeting [Originally in Box 163, Folder 1], 1968-1977 (Box 84)
  - RAM cells,1981 [Originally in Box 164, Folder 1], undated (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Paremecium, RAM cell [Originally in Box 164, Folder 2], undated (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - SRAM Cell [Originally in Box 164, Folder 3], undated (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Cells [Originally in Box 164, Folder 4], undated (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Cells [Originally in Box 164, Folder 6], undated (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - SRAM Cells [Originally in Box 164, Folder 7], undated (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Cells [Originally in Box 164, Folder 8], undated (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Cell electron micrographs [Originally in Box 164, Folder 9], undated (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Cell electron micrographs [Originally in Box 164, Folder 10], undated (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Cell electron micrographs [Originally in Box 164, Folder 11], undated (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Cell photographs [Originally in Box 164, Folder 12], undated (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Equipment [Originally in Box 164, Folder 18], undated (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Wafer comparison [Originally in Box 164, Folder 20], undated (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Simulation [Originally in Box 164, Folder 23], undated (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Microprocessor [Originally in Box 164, Folder 26], undated (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Microprocessor [Originally in Box 164, Folder 27], undated (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Mirocontroller [Originally in Box 164, Folder 28], undated (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Microprocessor [Originally in Box 164, Folder 29], undated (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Microprocessor [Originally in Box 164, Folder 30], undated (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Microprocessor [Originally in Box 164, Folder 31], undated (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Microprocessor [Originally in Box 164, Folder 32], undated (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Microprocessor [Originally in Box 164, Folder 33], undated (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Microprocessor [Originally in Box 164, Folder 34], undated (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Processor [Originally in Box 164, Folder 35], undated (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - Microcontroller [Originally in Box 164, Folder 36], undated (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - Memory Epsom [Originally in Box 164, Folder 37], undated (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - Mirocontroller [Originally in Box 164, Folder 38], undated (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - Microprocessor [Originally in Box 164, Folder 39], undated (Box 85, Folder 28)
  - Memory die [Originally in Box 164, Folder 40], undated (Box 85, Folder 29)
  - Microprocessor [Originally in Box 164, Folder 41], undated (Box 85, Folder 30)
  - Bipolar PROM [Originally in Box 164, Folder 42], undated (Box 85, Folder 31)
  - Bipolar PROM [Originally in Box 164, Folder 43], undated (Box 85, Folder 32)
  - Microprocessor [Originally in Box 164, Folder 44], undated (Box 85, Folder 33)
  - Microprocessor [Originally in Box 164, Folder 45], undated (Box 85, Folder 34)
  - Microprocessors [Originally in Box 164, Folder 46], undated (Box 85, Folder 35)
  - Microprocessors [Originally in Box 164, Folder 47], undated (Box 85, Folder 36)
  - Microprocessors [Originally in Box 164, Folder 48], undated (Box 85, Folder 37)
  - Microprocessor [Originally in Box 164, Folder 49], undated (Box 85, Folder 38)
  - Microprocessor [Originally in Box 164, Folder 50], undated (Box 85, Folder 39)
  - Microprocessor [Originally in Box 164, Folder 51], undated (Box 85, Folder 40)
  - Microprocessor [Originally in Box 164, Folder 52], undated (Box 85, Folder 41)
  - EPROM Evolution [Originally in Box 164, Folder 53], undated (Box 85, Folder 42)
  - Microprocessor [Originally in Box 164, Folder 54], undated (Box 85, Folder 43)
  - Magnetic tape and reticle [Originally in Box 164, Folder 55], undated (Box 85, Folder 44)
  - Plot and film [Originally in Box 164, Folder 56], undated (Box 85, Folder 45)
  - Plot and composite drawing [Originally in Box 164, Folder 57], undated (Box 85, Folder 46)
  - Master mask and wafer [Originally in Box 164, Folder 58], undated (Box 85, Folder 47)
  - Package assembly and finished [Originally in Box 164, Folder 59], undated (Box 85, Folder 48)
  - Censor [Originally in Box 164, Folder 62], undated (Box 85, Folder 49)
  - Legionnaires [Originally in Box 164, Folder 63], undated (Box 85, Folder 50)
  - Cell [Originally in Box 164, Folder 64], undated (Box 85, Folder 51)
  - Cells [Originally in Box 164, Folder 65], undated (Box 85, Folder 52)
  - Presentations for SIA Think Tank Meeting, Analysts Meeting, DISTI meeting, SEC Techron meetings [Originally in Box 164, Folder 68], undated (Box 85, Folder 53)
  - LSI Structures [Originally in Box 165, Folder 1], undated (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Circuits [Originally in Box 165, Folder 2], 1964 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Circuit [Originally in Box 165, Folder 3], 1968 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - 3101 and 1702 [Originally in Box 165, Folder 4], undated (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Passport photo, GEM [Originally in Box 165, Folder 5], 1972 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Circuit [Originally in Box 165, Folder 6], undated (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - 19th century images [Originally in Box 165, Folder 7], undated (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - End User Sales Conf. [Originally in Box 165, Folder 8], 1976 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Annual Shareholders meeting slides [Originally in Box 165, Folder 9], 1976 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Hillsboro plant drawing [Originally in Box 165, Folder 10], 1978 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - SEM of EPROM Cell [Originally in Box 165, Folder 11], undated (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Integrated circuit [Originally in Box 165, Folder 12], undated (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - BACUS Symposium [Originally in Box 165, Folder 13], 1984 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - 80386 MPU [Originally in Box 165, Folder 14], undated (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Noyce at SIA dinner (aka bird) [Originally in Box 165, Folder 15], undated (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Moore during SEMI [Originally in Box 165, Folder 16], 1985 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - GEM Chinese Ambassadors [Originally in Box 165, Folder 17], undated (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - GEM Visit to Japan [Originally in Box 165, Folder 18], 1986 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - RNN Dataquest presentation [Originally in Box 165, Folder 19], 1986 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - GEM visit to China [Originally in Box 165, Folder 20], 1987 (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Norwegian Academy [Originally in Box 165, Folder 21], 1987 (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Intel manufacturing facilities [Originally in Box 165, Folder 22], 1988 (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - Group photo GEM Japan visit [Originally in Box 165, Folder 23], 1988 (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - GEM at National Academy of Engineers awards [Originally in Box 165, Folder 24], undated (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - DVI screen samples [Originally in Box 165, Folder 25], undated (Box 86, Folder 25)
  - Poicy Board Members of Cornell's National Nanofabrication facility [Originally in Box 165, Folder 26], 1989 (Box 86, Folder 26)
  - Intel i860 and Touchstone Delta photos [Originally in Box 165, Folder 27], undated (Box 86, Folder 27)
  - Slides for Monte Jade presentation [Originally in Box 165, Folder 28], 1992 (Box 86, Folder 28)
  - International Electron device Conference [Originally in Box 165, Folder 29], 1996 (Box 86, Folder 29)
  - Fifty Years of Semiconductor Technology [Originally in Box 165, Folder 30], 1997 (Box 86, Folder 30)
  - GEM at Grinnell RNN Science Center dedication [Originally in Box 165, Folder 31], undated (Box 86, Folder 31)
  - Museum of American Heritage presentation [Originally in Box 165, Folder 32], 1998 (Box 86, Folder 32)
  - Message driven Processor for MIT [Originally in Box 165, Folder 33], 1992 (Box 86, Folder 33)
  - Edward and Maria Keonjian [Originally in Box 165, Folder 34], 1994 (Box 86, Folder 34)
  - Chartering boat [Originally in Box 165, Folder 35], 1996 (Box 86, Folder 35)
  - Robert Noyce photo [Originally in Box 165, Folder 36], undated (Box 86, Folder 36)
  - Technical Images from Jet Propulsion Laboratory [Originally in Box 165, Folder 37], undated (Box 86, Folder 37)
  - Statues and Plaques at CalTech [Originally in Box 165, Folder 38], undated (Box 86, Folder 38)
  - CalTech imaging [Originally in Box 165, Folder 39], undated (Box 86, Folder 39)
  - Caltech Board of Trustees [Originally in Box 165, Folder 40], 1998 (Box 86, Folder 40)
  - Caltech Board of Trustees [Originally in Box 165, Folder 41], 1991-2001 (Box 86, Folder 41)
  - Construction of Moore Laboratory at CalTech [Originally in Box 165, Folder 42], 1994 (Box 86, Folder 42)
  - Caltech board of Trustees [Originally in Box 165, Folder 43], 1983-1990 (Box 86, Folder 43)
  - GEMs trip to the Kayapo [Originally in Box 165, Folder 44], 1994 (Box 86, Folder 44)
  - Employees of the Ford Motor Company [Originally in Box 165, Folder 45], undated (Box 86, Folder 45)
  - Intel Quality Award [Originally in Box 165, Folder 46], 1992 (Box 86, Folder 46)
  - GEM Visit to IBM [Originally in Box 165, Folder 47], 1982 (Box 86, Folder 47)
  - Matsushita Electronics corporation visit to Intel [Originally in Box 165, Folder 48], 1987 (Box 86, Folder 48)
  - AMD 8086 MPU [Originally in Box 165, Folder 49], undated (Box 86, Folder 49)
  - Arjun and Veera Saxena [Originally in Box 165, Folder 50], undated (Box 86, Folder 50)
  - United Way Donation, 1988 [Originally in Box 165, Folder 51], undated (Box 86, Folder 51)
  - Silverking Oceanic Farm [Originally in Box 165, Folder 52], undated (Box 86, Folder 52)
  - GEM and the Accenti Family [Originally in Box 165, Folder 53], undated (Box 86, Folder 53)
  - Hawaiian Sales Meeting [Originally in Box 165, Folder 54], undated (Box 86, Folder 54)
- Series 5: Audiovisual Materials, 1975-2002
  This series consists of 143 VHS format tapes and 21 audiocassette tapes from Moore’s collection at Intel Corp. The audiocassette tapes contain recordings of Moore discussing Silicon Valley and the semiconductor industry during interviews, programs, and conferences. There are also 12 tapes from an oral history interview with Moore. The topics of the videocassettes include Intel Corporation, SEMATECH, Conservation International, Caltech, United Way, award ceremonies, conferences, seminars, interviews, and healthcare.
  This material has been digitized and is available in the Special Collections reading room or via Searchworks for Stanford-affiliated patrons.
  - Caltech Jet Propulsion Lab Res. Conference: LSI and MPU [Originally in Box 166], March 1975 (Box 87, Audiocassettes 1)
  - Robert Noyce Story [Originally in Box 166], 1997 (Box 87, Audiocassettes 2)
  - GEM Bay Area Council, Outlook Conference [Originally in Box 166], 1985 (Box 87, Audiocassettes 3)
  - Consumer Business Radio, Dennis Carter Interview [Originally in Box 166], 1991 (Box 87, Audiocassettes 4)
  - All Things Considered NPR [Originally in Box 166], 1997 (Box 87, Audiocassettes 5)
  - BBC Transistor Programs, Discovery, U751 [Originally in Box 166], 1988 (Box 87, Audiocassettes 6)
  - CCC Conference (Corporate Capabilities and Competitiveness) [Originally in Box 167], 1990 (Box 88, Videotapes 1)
  - Intel Corp. In Celebration of Grand Challenge Computing [Originally in Box 167], 1992 (Box 88, Videotapes 2)
  - Intel Corp. Microma Watches Denver and Microma Watches NY [Originally in Box 167], 1975 (Box 88, Videotapes 3)
  - Intel: The Microcomputer Company [Originally in Box 167], undated (Box 88, Videotapes 4)
  - MIT: Very Large Scale Integration Seminar, More Presenation "VLSI Industry Trends, Technological and Economic" [Originally in Box 167], undated (Box 88, Videotapes 5)
  - Stanford Instruction Television Network: Prof. Allison [Originally in Box 167], 1990 (Box 88, Videotapes 6)
  - American Business with Lee McCarthy [Originally in Box 167], undated (Box 88, Videotapes 7)
  - Intel Corp. The Computer Inside Story [Originally in Box 167], 1991 (Box 88, Videotapes 8)
  - Robert Reed Interview (Science Bowl) CNN [Originally in Box 167], 1991 (Box 88, Videotapes 9)
  - National Semiconductor Final Version [Originally in Box 167], 1991 (Box 88, Videotapes 10)
  - Intel Broadcasts: Computer Chronicles, ABC Business World, CNBC Market Wrap, KVBC News, KLAS News, National Public Radio [Originally in Box 167], 1991 (Box 88, Videotapes 11)
  - The Computerworld Smithsonian Awards "A Search for New Heros" [Originally in Box 167], 1991 (Box 88, Videotapes 12)
  - Conservation International Nintey-Two Report [Originally in Box 167], 1992 (Box 88, Videotapes 13)
  - Andy Grove on ABC Business World [Originally in Box 167], 1992 (Box 88, Videotapes 14)
  - Intel FlashFile Memory Introduction Testimonials [Originally in Box 167], 1992 (Box 88, Videotapes 15)
  - Intel Corp "Awesome Applications" [Originally in Box 168], 1994 (Box 88, Videotapes 16)
  - Semiconductor Research Corp. 10th Anniversary A Decade of Service to the Semiconductor Industry [Originally in Box 168], 1992 (Box 88, Videotapes 17)
  - Gordon Moore on Moneyline [Originally in Box 168], 1993 (Box 88, Videotapes 18)
  - Andy Grove on This Week with David Brinkley [Originally in Box 168], 1993 (Box 88, Videotapes 19)
  - Intel Good Morning America; Demo of Business Communication Technology [Originally in Box 168], 1993 (Box 88, Videotapes 20)
  - PBS Nightly Business Report Interview with GEM [Originally in Box 168], 1993 (Box 88, Videotapes 21)
  - Slovenian TV Program: GEM Interview [Originally in Box 168], undated (Box 88, Videotapes 22)
  - Intel Corp: The Ubiquitous PC Keynote by Andy Grove [Originally in Box 168], 1994 (Box 89, Videotapes 1)
  - Intel Comdex Convergence Keynote Andy Grove [Originally in Box 168], 1994 (Box 89, Videotapes 2)
  - Dataquest 20th Anniversary Conference presentation by GEM [Originally in Box 168], 1995 (Box 89, Videotapes 3)
  - Silicon Genesis; Interview with C Lester Hogan [Originally in Box 168], 1995 (Box 89, Videotapes 4)
  - Novellus "What About Bob?" Bob Graham video profile [Originally in Box 168], 1995 (Box 89, Videotapes 5)
  - Intel Corp Andrew Grove/Intel on Charlie Rose Show [Originally in Box 168], 1995 (Box 89, Videotapes 6)
  - Intel Corp: 60 Minutes - Chip Theft Story [Originally in Box 168], 1995 (Box 89, Videotapes 7)
  - Corporate Rainforest Campaign [Originally in Box 168], undated (Box 89, Videotapes 8)
  - GEM Silicon Valley Business [Originally in Box 169], 1995 (Box 89, Videotapes 9)
  - Horatio Alger Awards Awardee Bios [Originally in Box 169], 1996 (Box 89, Videotapes 10)
  - Horatio Alger Awards Program [Originally in Box 169], 1995 (Box 89, Videotapes 11)
  - Caltech: Moving Towards 21st Century [Originally in Box 169], 1995 (Box 89, Videotapes 12)
  - ABC News Night Line SI Pegasus Planet Discovery [Originally in Box 169], 1995 (Box 89, Videotapes 13)
  - Intel; Telecom '95 Keynote by Andy Grove [Originally in Box 169], undated (Box 89, Videotapes 14)
  - Why Get Involved? United Way [Originally in Box 169], 1995 (Box 89, Videotapes 15)
  - Conservation International BBC Horizons: Nature's Numbers [Originally in Box 169], 1996 (Box 89, Videotapes 16)
  - Horatio Alger Awards: Only in America [Originally in Box 169], 1996 (Box 89, Videotapes 17)
  - Horatio Alger Awards Awardee Bios [Originally in Box 169], 1996 (Box 89, Videotapes 18)
  - SETI Institute: Geoff Marcy Preentaion on "The Hunt for Planets" [Originally in Box 169], 1996 (Box 89, Videotapes 19)
  - Horatio Alger Awards Herman Gain [Originally in Box 169], 1996 (Box 89, Videotapes 20)
  - Triumph of the Nerds [Originally in Box 170], 1996 (Box 89, Videotapes 21)
  - The Keck II Observatory Dedication Dinner [Originally in Box 169], 1996 (Box 89, Videotapes 22)
  - Triumph of the Nerds Act I and II [Originally in Box 170], 1966 (Box 90, Videotape 1)
  - Intel Corp MMX Compilation Tape #2 [Originally in Box 170], undated (Box 90, Videotape 2)
  - The Money Wheel with GEM [Originally in Box 170], 1997 (Box 90, Videotape 3)
  - Foundation for the National Medals of Science/Technology, Awards Ceremony, White House [Originally in Box 170], 1996 (Box 90, Videotape 4)
  - Intel-Comdex Video: Federico Faggin and Ted Hoff [Originally in Box 170], 1996 (Box 90, Videotape 5)
  - KICU Reaching for the Stars Profiles [Originally in Box 170], 1996 (Box 90, Videotape 6)
  - MPU 25th Anniversary Press Conference in Tokyo, Nikkei Satellite [Originally in Box 170], 1996 (Box 90, Videotape 7)
  - Japanese written NHK [Originally in Box 170], 1996 (Box 90, Videotape 8)
  - Scripps Institute: Explorations [Originally in Box 170], undated (Box 90, Videotape 9)
  - K2 Comm: The Detwiler Foundation Computers for Schools Program for the National Governors' Association [Originally in Box 170], 1997 (Box 90, Videotape 10)
  - University of Cambridge: Electron Centennial Meeting, Cavendish Lab [Originally in Box 170], 1977 (Box 90, Videotape 11)
  - How'd They Do That with Gordon Moore, TLC [Originally in Box 170], 1997 (Box 90, Videotape 12)
  - Intel Compaq Innovate Andy Grove Keynote [Originally in Box 170], 1997 (Box 90, Videotape 13)
  - IEEE Honors Ceremony [Originally in Box 170], 1997 (Box 90, Videotape 14)
  - GEM on "How'd They do That?" TLC Cable [Originally in Box 170], 1997 (Box 90, Videotape 15)
  - R. Stanton Avery Memorial [Originally in Box 170], 1997 (Box 90, Videotape 16)
  - National Science & Technology Medals Foundation "Our Story" [Originally in Box 170], undated (Box 90, Videotape 17)
  - Charting the Course: The next 50 years [Originally in Box 171], 1997 (Box 90, Videotape 18)
  - 1998 National Science and Technology Medals Laureates [Originally in Box 169] (Box 90, Videotape 19)
  - Origin of Silicon Valley with GEM [Originally in Box 171], 1998 (Box 90, Videotape 20)
  - Semiconductor Research Corp. Competitiveness Foundation "VISION" Program [Originally in Box 172], undated (Box 90, Videotape 21)
  - Silicon Valley Story [Originally in Box 172], undated (Box 90, Videotape 22)
  - Smithsonian: GEM I/V [Originally in Box 172], undated (Box 90, Videotape 23)
  - Intel Corp. The Impact of Integrated Circuits [Originally in Box 172], undated (Box 90, Videotape 24)
  - BancAmerica: 50th Anniversary of the Semiconductor Industry [Originally in Box 171], 1998 (Box 91, Videotape 1)
  - The Newshour with Jim Lehrer GEM and Steve Smith [Originally in Box 171], 1998 (Box 91, Videotape 2)
  - 1998 National Science and Technology Medals Laureates [Originally in Box 171] (Box 91, Videotape 3)
  - Intel Corp. Andrew Grove Exploratorium [Originally in Box 171], undated (Box 91, Videotape 4)
  - Frontline: Washington's Other Scandal [Originally in Box 171], 1998 (Box 91, Videotape 5)
  - Dr. Stephing Hawking Lecture, SJ State Univ [Originally in Box 171], 1998 (Box 91, Videotape 6)
  - National Medals of Science & Technology: White House Ceremony [Originally in Box 171], 1999 (Box 91, Videotape 7)
  - Intel Museum [Originally in Box 171], 1999 (Box 91, Videotape 8)
  - APS: GEM Presentation on 20th Century Development in Instrumentation and Measurement [Originally in Box 171], 2000 (Box 91, Videotape 9)
  - Stanford Institute for Economic Policy Research SIEPR Marketing Tape [Originally in Box 171], 2000 (Box 91, Videotape 10)
  - ABC News Gordon Moore Retires and Aliens-SETI [Originally in Box 171], undated (Box 91, Videotape 11)
  - Intel Corp Moore's Law [Originally in Box 171], 2001 (Box 91, Videotape 12)
  - "Less is Moore" 14th Annual Distinguished Citizens Award [Originally in Box 171], 2001 (Box 91, Videotape 13)
  - Pat Gelsinger presentation re: Moore's Law at IDF [Originally in Box 171], 2002 (Box 91, Videotape 14)
  - Frankin Institute Awards Convocation [Originally in Box 171], 2002 (Box 91, Videotape 15)
  - A Celebration of Caltech Science "The Brain" by Chistof Koch [Originally in Box 171], 2002 (Box 91, Videotape 16)
  - A Celebration of Caltech Science "The Earth and the Universe" by Andrew Lange [Originally in Box 172], 2002 (Box 91, Videotape 17)
  - The Detwiler Foundation Computer for Schools Program [Originally in Box 172], undated (Box 91, Videotape 18)
  - Discover CalTech [Originally in Box 172], undated (Box 91, Videotape 19)
  - Horatio Alger Award, GEM and Les Vadasz [Originally in Box 172], undated (Box 91, Videotape 20)
  - Intel Corp B-Roll [Originally in Box 172], undated (Box 91, Videotape 21)
  - Intel Corp GEM B-Roll [Originally in Box 172], undated (Box 91, Videotape 22)
  - Intel Corp GEM [Originally in Box 172], undated (Box 91, Videotape 23)
  - Who are engineers? You? [Originally in Box 172], undated (Box 91, Videotape 24)
  - United Way: Tocqueville Today: Million Dollar Giving [Originally in Box 172], undated (Box 91, Videotape 25)